(Howard:)- You could wear it again sometime.
- Where?
(Howard:)I don't know, hunting?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Don't forget to talk to her
about this meshugas...
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)...where I don't get grandkids.
(Howard:)Don't worry, Ma, I will,
as soon as I can figure out...
(Howard:)...a way to bring up
such a sensitive issue.
(Bernadette:)- Guess you talked to your mom.
l was upset.
(Howard:)My mom can be
a pretty good shoulder to cry on...
(Howard:)...if the smell of Bengay
doesn't burn your eyes.
(Bernadette:)Look, it's obvious having kids
is really important to you...
(Bernadette:)...and I think I came up
with a solution.
(Howard:)Really? That's great. What?
(Bernadette:)Well, seeing as how I make
way more money than you anyway...
(Bernadette:)...what if I work
and you stay home with the kids?
(Sheldon:)- Me?
- Yeah.
(Bernadette:)You know, you'll watch Barney
and pull Cheerios out of their noses...
(Bernadette:)...and go on play dates and I'll work
and have conversations...
(Bernadette:)...with people my own age
and enjoy my life.
(Bernadette:)- Yeah.
- Yay! So we're good.
(Howard:)Yeah, we're good.
(Bernadette:)I don't know if this counted as a fight...
(Bernadette:)...but how about some make-up sex?
(Howard:)I would love that.
But what is that behind your ear?
(Howard:)Oh, look, it's a condom.